https://www.navisite.com/privacy-policy/

Close Search
Search for:
Industries
Business ServicesEducationEnergy & UtilitiesHealthcareFinancialManufacturingRetail
Company
AboutCareersLeadershipNewsPress ReleasesRisk and Compliance#NaviGivesBackContact
Home / Privacy Policy
Data Privacy
Learn about our unwavering commitment to comply with data privacy laws and regulations, so we can protect what’s most important to us—your business.
Contact Us
Contact Us
Protecting the privacy and confidentiality of your information is our priority.
Building a trusted relationship with you is our number one priority—and that starts by protecting your personal information. From complying with applicable data privacy laws and regulations, to doing business with the highest ethical standards, to abiding by a robust internal data protection program—we’re committed to keeping your personal information safe. Data confidentiality, integrity and availability are our founding values, and our designated data privacy team ensures that our people, processes and services embody these values in everything we do.
How Do We Protect You?
Data Privacy Policy
Learn how we protect customer information through a detailed Privacy Policy that outlines our data collection, usage, maintenance, protection and disclosure processes.
Read More
Regulatory Compliance
We maintain strict adherence to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act privacy laws (CCPA) to keep your personal data safe.
Read More
Data Subject Access Requests
Our team follows all the proper procedures for handling Data Subject Access Requests under GDPR.
Read More
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
We are committed to being transparent about the use of cookies and other related technologies on our website.
Read More
Get Started Today
Contact Us
Contact Us
We use cookiesThis website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Accept CookiesPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
